Cute.
It's precious
It's fun
Hello
Oh, my God!
I've been wanting to come here for a long time.
I'm here at Hachi-Cafe!
It looks like this.
Now let's get going!
Nice staircase!
Wow, wow, wow!
Can you see it? Look, it's a good start!
Look, look, this door.
Maybe it's these reptilian scales.
Very elaborate!
Well, I'll get right to it.
Push.
Excuse me. Good morning.
Good morning.
It's warm. The bees are so hot.
Look at this bee figure!
I have one of these from the junkyard.
I like bees so much that I collect them.
Choro-Q, the cockroach!
Okay, I'll go in now.
Oh, it's so cute! Its eyes are so cute!
What are you doing with your hands like this?
He's got three fingers, and he did it on purpose.
Too cute! Cute!
She was getting close. She thought she could climb.
I see... she thinks I'm a tree branch.
I can't recognize the glass.
I see, I'm not a tree, I'm Kira.
My name is Kira. Call me Kira Court.
I'm Hashimoto-san. I'm Masumoto. We look alike.
But he gets so close to me, I'm very satisfied even without touching him.
I didn't expect him to get this close.
If you like, I can just put in the music glass.
Is that okay?
If you get too close, he climbs on your head.
Oh, it's so 3D!
Don't let it climb up.
Are you okay?
If he knows he can't get out, he'll give up.
You're a smart girl.
He's a smart boy.
She keeps trying to grab the glass.
So cute!
Chameleons are so smart.
It's like a dinosaur. This is the tosakarigent.
The tosakari gentian is a characteristic of the chameleon over the world.
So cute!
I think my favorite thing about reptiles is that they look like they're smiling when you look at them from the front.
Where can I touch it?
I like the way you stroke it.
She has a habit of being a little uncomfortable here.
Excuse me.
Oh! Can you hold this in your hand?
What do you mean?
A body lengthwise? Oh, my God!
I'm not very good at this.
I really love your hands.
So cute!
I have a leopard gecko at home.
You have a Leocha?
Yes, I do! So I'd love to meet her.
Leoca, she's over there at the end of the hall.
Oh, hello! So many!
They're so big!
Their skin tone is a little different.
And all the stuff... it really stands out.
They're so cute.
Maybe it's tangerine.
Tangerine.
Tangerine orange popsicles.
Get me some...
Oh, he's so cute.
Hi. - Hi.
It's a little tricky.
It's a little bit... Oh, there it is.
He's cute.
No, look, he's smiling.
I can tell if it's a boy or a girl by their faces. Can I try?
I'll just use your face.
It's a girl.
Oh, you're right.
Yes!
New, new gun girl.
Oh, I'm back in seltzer.
So cute.
Cute.
She looks a bit like Leopa.
I wanted to keep Nisyahu and his family, but I heard that it is a little harder to raise them than Leopa,
But I heard that it is a little more difficult to raise them than Leopas.
That's true. They are a little more nervous than Leopas.
But they are cute.
They are cute.
Black eyes.Black eyes.
Cute.
Oh, what a cutie.
It has a blue tongue.
The one named "blue-tailed lizard"?
Yeah, the blue-tailed lizard is on this side, though,
Same kind of mosquito.
It looks like a form, doesn't it?
Yes, that's right. The kind of lizard that is called what kind of form skink.
Cute.
This is the one with eyelashes.
This is the one with eyelashes. This is a cress.
He's cute.
Oh, no.
She's really cute.
I'll have to get some eye drops.
You're right. Keep your eyes open. Lick your eyes with your tongue to get the dryness out.
Junior high school students are smart.
They're cute.
He's a good boy. You can touch him anywhere.
You don't mind if I touch him?
So this is what it's like.
There are many people who wear half-length bracelets and go for a walk in the park.
I'll help you. You have beautiful eyes.
You have beautiful eyes.
What?
They're cute.
It's warm.
Somehow.
You just did a great isolation, moving your neck like this.
Yes, that. It's like mobbing.
Are you happy?
She is happy. Maybe she's a little excited.
It's cute.
I'm doing it again.
Aren't I good at it?
You didn't see it, did you?
I saw it at first.
I looked away right away.
Most of the customers do it, too.
They start imitating me.
What? Is it real?
Yes, it's real.
Oh, my God!
It looks fake.
It looks a little bit...
What are those horns on the nose?
It's just like a real horn.
Horns?
I don't think you have that many on your hands.
That's the first time I've ever seen one this close up.
You did it.
It's the first Iguana I've ever seen.
Really?
So cute!
What? You're cute.
You can stretch it all the way down its neck.
You don't mind?
Yes, you can.
Nanchan!
You're so cute!
It's called a grapple.
Grapple!
Yes, it's called "nobokare".
You can get it on the bottom of a chicken's face.
Oh!
It's warm!
Reptiles are so warm.
It's nice to feel their body heat.
Yes, they are.
So cute!
This is how they raise their body temperature.
What a cutie!
So, she's attached to me.
Just support him on the bottom, and he'll be fine.
Just don't bend her back.
Not back?
I have to move from here.
Are you sure?
It's cute, but it weighs a lot.
It's heavy. It weighs a little over 3 kilos.
Heh.
It's like I'm holding a child in my arms.
Oh, it's so cute!
Oh, this is something.
I didn't realize they were attached like this.
The color is beautiful.
The color is beautiful. It's going to get warmer and warmer as it gets warmer.
It really looks like a dinosaur!
When it's this big...
Oh, my God, I opened my face. It's so warm.
I've been looking at it from behind the screen.
Thank you for everything.
You've got vertical lines in your dark eyes.
And Lissade's got a pair of eyes.
He's so cool. He's so cool.
He's so cute!
It's precious.
It's like a weight...Sleek and weighty.
Cute.
Can I ask you to show the front view?
She's really cute.
Smile.
Thank you. Really cute.
Or a snake.
Can I wear a snake around my neck?
By all means. I've got some hikeribs over here that I can wrap around my neck.
Are these the ones with the famous mosquito, the ball python?
Yes, sir. You know them well.
Which one should I choose? Which one would suit you?
She's so cute.
The second one from the top. Her name is Dorongo.
Doronjo.
Doronjo, but her name is Yatterman.
I know him.
Her name is Doronjo-sama.
Her motif is a skull and a heart.
There's a skull and a heart mark here.
It's amazing!
It's Doronjo-sama, isn't it?
It's Doronjo-sama.
I know, I know. He's the one who leaves, right?
I know, I know.
You seem to be suited to heart marks and the like.
I'm glad. Let's take Doronjo in our arms for a minute.
Shall I hold her in my arms first?
May I?
Be careful not to touch the snake's face.
Doronjo!
Oh, you're so sturdy!
You're so docile, aren't you?
So docile. Amazing.
So cute.
Pero is so cute!
And for such a tiny face, he eats very big food.
Yes, he does.
Is it true that he has his jawbone removed?
That's amazing.
Then let's have you ride on my neck for a minute, Tronjo-chan.
Wow, it's huge! So this is what it feels like.
I feel like she's really alive.
What? He's so cute!
He's so cute!
Oh, you should wear a neck brace! So cute!
He's cute!
Haven't you seen any snakes in the wild since you came to Tokyo?
I once found one on my way to school.
I found one on my way to school and brought it to school.
I got so mad at it.
I've always loved snakes that much.
I'm so happy that my dream came true.
I'm thinking of having Kugame-chan feed it to me.
I'd love to!
She'll eat if you hold it in front of her face.
I understand.
It's a little heavy.
Eat.
Eat it!
He's cute.
I love rice more than anything.
You're dexterous with just your face.
Yes, it is.
Sorry for a second, Tongo.
You're cool, you.
By the way, he's just a kid.
Wow, he's big.
That's amazing.
It has a life span of about 40 years, and it's still just a kid.
Don't turtles live 10,000 years?
Turtles live 10,000 years? I hope they live.
Cranes live 1,000 years.
Is that a lie?
No, I want to believe it's not a lie.
Good. Can I hold it if it looks like you have it?
Can I hold it?
You can hold it.
That's great.
I think I can do it.
Excuse me.
Oh, wow.
This is probably the heaviest thing I've ever carried.
You must be able to carry such a heavy body by yourself.
Your muscles are amazing, too, aren't they?
Oh my, oh my.
I used to go to Hachi-Well Cafe in private,
I didn't want to go to a place where there were too many kinds of animals I could touch,
They were really cute. I could tell that they were really loved and nurtured.
That's all I have to say about the Hachiu Cafe. Thank you very much.